

NEW ZEALAND CITIZEN

WEST AUCKLAND, 0610 0210393541

RAGHAV.SIDHARTH@LIVE.COM





REFERENCES AVAILABLE
ON REQUEST

EDUCATION

CERTIFICATE IN APPLIED SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

Dev Academy Aotearoa JAN 2023 - APR 2023

MASTERS IN DESIGN & VISUAL ARTS

Media Design School 2018 - 2019

POSTGRADUATE DIPLOMA IN DESIGN & VISUAL ARTS

Media Design School 2018 - 2019

BACHELORS OF DESIGN & VISUAL ARTS

UNITEC Institute of Technology 2015 - 2017

CERTIFICATE IN DESIGN & VISUAL ARTS

UNITEC Institute of Technology 2014 - 2015

INTERESTS & HOBBIES

I'm passionate about exploring new horizons and challenging myself in every way possible. From boxing to writing and producing short-films, design to reading books, I have diverse interests that keep me on my toes!

COMPETITIONS

VF48 HOUR FILM COMPETITION

Exhibited "RESERVED" 2022

VF48 HOUR FILM COMPETITION Exhibited "SkuXX Dogs 4 Life" 2021

RAGHAV SIDHARTH

Full Stack Software Developer

SUMMARY

My passion for technology and an unbridled sense of curiosity led me to pursue the wide, wonderful world of software development. I aim to apply my newfound skills to make beautiful, accessible applications for users to engage with.

Prior, I had been a practising graphic designer for over four years, specialising in print, packaging, and identity design. My goal throughout my career has been to facilitate the needs of small and large businesses, utilising e-commerce solutions and eDM marketing strategies to grow and reach new customers.

KEY SKILLS

Full Stack Website Development

Throughout the challenging seventeen-week code boot camp, I was pleasantly surprised by the extensive variety of new skills I had acquired and the vast wealth of knowledge I had gained. My proficiency with advanced tools such as React, JavaScript, TypeScript, SQLite 3, Redux, and Tailwind has deepened, and I now possess a profound understanding and appreciation of the intricacies of web development. I am eager to continue learning and expanding my expertise in this rapidly-evolving industry.

Soft Skills

I've had the pleasure of collaborating with a diverse group of individuals across various projects and professional settings. As a team leader, I've learned to cultivate a professional and approachable demeanor, which enables others to feel comfortable sharing their thoughts and concerns. Some of my strengths include clear communication, the ability to deliver engaging presentations to non-technical audiences, and a natural sense of empathy towards others. During my time at Dev Academy, I honed these skills and had the opportunity to practice giving constructive feedback and engaging in non-violent communication with my peers. The intensive nature of the program allowed me to further develop these abilities and improve upon my existing skill set.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Full Employment History available on second page.



NEW ZEALAND CITIZEN

WEST AUCKLAND, 0610 0210393541

RAGHAV.SIDHARTH@LIVE.COM





REFERENCES AVAILABLE
ON REQUEST

EDUCATION

CERTIFICATE IN APPLIED SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

Dev Academy Aotearoa JAN 2023 - APR 2023

MASTERS IN DESIGN & VISUAL ARTS

Media Design School 2018 - 2019

POSTGRADUATE DIPLOMA IN DESIGN & VISUAL ARTS

Media Design School 2018 - 2019

BACHELORS OF DESIGN & VISUAL ARTS

UNITEC Institute of Technology 2015 - 2017

CERTIFICATE IN DESIGN & VISUAL ARTS

UNITEC Institute of Technology 2014 - 2015

INTERESTS & HOBBIES

I'm passionate about exploring new horizons and challenging myself in every way possible. From boxing to writing and producing short-films, design to reading books, I have diverse interests that keep me on my toes!

COMPETITIONS

VF48 HOUR FILM COMPETITION

Exhibited "RESERVED" 2022

VF48 HOUR FILM COMPETITION Exhibited "SkuXX Dogs 4 Life"

RAGHAV SIDHARTH

Full Stack Software Developer

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT - DEV ACADEMY AOTEAROA

JAN 2023 - APR 2023

Project <u>Gallerina</u> marked the end of a rigorous seventeenweek boot camp at Dev Academy. Our team worked together to construct and showcase a Full Stack React application that leveraged the capabilities of SQLite 3, Tailwind CSS, TypeScript, and an external RESTful API.

As part of my responsibilities, I collaborated with my partner to gather data from the API and create several Frontend components.

CUSTOMER ENGAGEMENT CONSULTANT - LOTTO NZ

AUG 2022 - DEC 2022

This role involved meticulously examining damaged physical ticket claims using data provided by both customers and retailers. It was a demanding position that required a great deal of focus and patience.

CUSTOMER SERVICE SUPPORT - ASB BANK

APR 2022 - JUN 2022

This job involved delivering outstanding customer service for one of New Zealand's biggest banks. It was quite a demanding position with a consistently heavy workload, which called for quick thinking to provide customers with effective solutions.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER - BANUS.CO.NZ

2014 - 2023

Developed various digital and physical promotional material: eDM marketing, banners for physical events, recipe guides/books, video format recipe guides and much more. Managed Shopify sales channel: stock update/changes, bug fixing and product photography.